You should know clearly
يجب أن تعرف بوضوح
that being with me
أن تكون معي
comes with a price.
يأتي ذلك بثمن.
Whatever you want to do,
مهما كان ما تريد فعله،
is fine.
لا بأس.
All right.
حسنًا.
You said it yourself.
لقد قلتها بنفسك.
Whatever I want,
كل ما أريده،
is fine.
لا بأس.
Today,
اليوم،
I'm going to make your life
سأجعل حياتك
a living hell,
جحيم حيّ،
unable to live or die.
غير قادر على الحياة أو الموت.
We've been through so much together.
لقد مررنا بالكثير معاً.
Do you
هل أنت
have no empathy at all?
ألا يملكون أي تعاطف على الإطلاق؟
A marriage of convenience is just rubbish.
الزواج المصلحي مجرد هراء.
Since you want to marry me so much,
بما أنك ترغبين بالزواج مني بشدة،
fine.
بخير.
Then I'll let you experience
ثم سأتركك تجرب
what is called
ما يسمى
the joys of marriage.
أفراح الزواج.
Aren't they overacting a bit?
ألا يبالغون قليلاً في ردة فعلهم؟
But
لكن
users love watching this kind of thing now.
يحب المستخدمون مشاهدة هذا النوع من الأشياء الآن.
They really look like a couple.
يبدوان حقاً كزوجين.
I just want you to understand
أريدك فقط أن تفهم
that my feelings for you
هذه هي مشاعري تجاهك
have nothing to do with family,
لا علاقة لها بالعائلة،
nothing to do with marriage.
لا علاقة للأمر بالزواج.
It's simply because I love you.
الأمر ببساطة لأنني أحبك.
They are acting really well.
إنهم يتصرفون بشكل جيد للغاية.
This doesn't look like acting.
هذا لا يبدو تمثيلاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You guys.
يا رفاق.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
So tell me.
أخبرني إذن.
Today,
اليوم،
what story are you making up
ما القصة التي تختلقها؟
to trick this old man?
هل تريد خداع هذا الرجل العجوز؟
I'm getting old.
أنا أتقدم في السن.
You want me to watch your soap opera?
هل تريدني أن أشاهد مسلسلك التلفزيوني؟
Chairman,
رئيس مجلس الإدارة،
I didn't mean to hide it from you for so many years.
لم أكن أنوي إخفاء الأمر عنك طوال هذه السنوات.
Be honest.
كن صادقاً.
When did you get together?
متى بدأت علاقتكما؟
Dad.
أب.
Eight years.
ثماني سنوات.
We've been together since high school.
لقد كنا معًا منذ المدرسة الثانوية.
Let her speak for herself.
دعها تتحدث عن نفسها.
Speak.
يتكلم.
It's been eight years.
لقد مرّت ثماني سنوات.
I knew something was up with you two long ago.
كنت أعرف أن هناك شيئاً ما يحدث معك منذ زمن طويل.
And you two.
وأنتما الاثنان.
What is going on with you two?
ما الذي يحدث بينكما؟
Didn't you tell us it was fake?
ألم تخبرنا أنه مزيف؟
How did it become real?
كيف أصبح ذلك حقيقة؟
Dad.
أب.
Uncle.
عم.
We just
لقد قمنا فقط
renewed our contract.
جددنا عقدنا.
Don't just stand there.
لا تقف هناك فقط.
It's the weekend.
إنها عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
Go out on a date, hurry.
اخرج في موعد غرامي، أسرع.
Don't be an eyesore here.
لا تكن مصدر إزعاج هنا.
Go on, leave.
انصرف.
Go, go, go.
إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Go on.
هيا.
Dad.
أب.
We already have proof of our love.
لدينا بالفعل دليل على حبنا.
This is...
هذا هو...
it's the fruit of love.
إنها ثمرة الحب.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
I'm waiting for my grandson to call me Grandpa.
أنتظر أن يناديني حفيدي بـ"جدو".
Dear friends,
أصدقائي الأعزاء،
today,
اليوم،
I want to announce some news.
أريد أن أعلن بعض الأخبار.
I
أنا
am getting married.
سأتزوج.
Ou Lu.
أنت لو.
Although for us,
على الرغم من أننا،
today is an ordinary day,
اليوم يوم عادي،
every day after today
كل يوم بعد اليوم
will be extraordinary.
سيكون الأمر استثنائياً.
Because today,
لأن اليوم،
you are going to
سوف تذهب
propose to me.
اطلب يدي.
All our romantic past
كل ماضينا الرومانسي
has become a vision for the future.
أصبحت رؤية للمستقبل.
After going through the eighty-one trials,
بعد خوض التجارب الـ 81،
as long as we can get the prize in the end,
طالما أننا نستطيع الحصول على الجائزة في النهاية،
nothing else matters.
لا شىئ اخر يهم.
Ou Lu,
أنت لو،
it's time to claim the prize.
حان وقت استلام الجائزة.
Miss Qixing,
الآنسة تشيكسينغ،
will you marry me?
هل ستتزوجني؟
I do.
أفعل.
To the darlings in the livestream today
إلى الأعزاء في البث المباشر اليوم
witnessing my happy moment,
أشهد لحظتي السعيدة،
go to my fan group right now
انضموا إلى مجموعة المعجبين الخاصة بي الآن
to get a coupon for 80 off 100.
للحصول على قسيمة خصم بقيمة 80 من 100.
See you at our next livestream.
نراكم في البث المباشر القادم.
Bye!
الوداع!
Those two are way too romantic.
هذان الاثنان رومانسيان للغاية.
This is my resume.
هذه سيرتي الذاتية.
Please
لو سمحت
have a look, interviewer.
ألقِ نظرة، أيها المحاور.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then please introduce yourself.
ثم تفضل بتقديم نفسك.
Hello, interviewer.
مرحباً أيها المحاور.
My name is Wen Pei'an.
اسمي وين بي آن.
I graduated from the University of Oxford.
تخرجت من جامعة أكسفورد.
I have been interning at your company for six months now.
أعمل كمتدرب في شركتكم منذ ستة أشهر.
The internship period has just ended.
انتهت فترة التدريب للتو.
Now,
الآن،
I very much want to become a full-time employee.
أرغب بشدة في أن أصبح موظفاً بدوام كامل.
Then tell me,
ثم أخبرني،
why are you so determined to stay at our company?
لماذا أنت مصممٌ جداً على البقاء في شركتنا؟
During the internship period,
خلال فترة التدريب،
I experienced a sense of
لقد شعرت بشعور من
wonderful fulfillment I've never felt before.
شعور رائع بالإنجاز لم أشعر به من قبل.
Therefore,
لذلك،
I really want to become a full-time employee.
أرغب بشدة في أن أصبح موظفاً بدوام كامل.
To be able to become your company's
لكي تتمكن من أن تصبح جزءًا من شركتك
long-term partner,
شريك طويل الأمد،
and grow together.
وننمو معاً.
Tell me about something
أخبرني عن شيء ما
you found
لقد وجدت
most memorable during your internship.
أكثر اللحظات التي لا تُنسى خلال فترة تدريبك.
During this time,
خلال هذه الفترة،
every day,
كل يوم،
every hour,
كل ساعة،
every moment,
في كل لحظة،
every minute,
كل دقيقة،
every second
كل ثانية
left a deep impression on me.
لقد تركت انطباعاً عميقاً في نفسي.
What are your strengths?
ما هي نقاط قوتك؟
Wealthy.
ثري.
Good physique.
بنية جسدية جيدة.
High educational background.
خلفية تعليمية عالية.
And your weaknesses?
وما هي نقاط ضعفك؟
My weakness is
نقطة ضعفي هي
being too much of a perfectionist.
كونه شخصًا يسعى للكمال أكثر من اللازم.
But during this time,
لكن خلال هذا الوقت،
I deeply
أنا بعمق
came to understand
فهمت
that perfection
ذلك الكمال
is built from countless imperfections.
مبني من عيوب لا حصر لها.
And these
وهذه
seemingly imperfect things
أشياء تبدو غير كاملة
are even more memorable.
بل إنها أكثر رسوخاً في الذاكرة.
So, do you think
إذن، هل تعتقد ذلك؟
you yourself are qualified for this job?
هل أنت مؤهل لهذه الوظيفة؟
I have made thorough preparations,
لقد قمتُ باستعدادات شاملة،
and during the internship period,
وخلال فترة التدريب،
I also gained some
لقد اكتسبت أيضاً بعضاً
in-depth understanding of your company.
فهم متعمق لشركتك.
I don't know if I
لا أعرف إن كنت
can shoulder this responsibility,
بإمكانه تحمل هذه المسؤولية،
but
لكن
I will definitely give it my all
سأبذل قصارى جهدي بالتأكيد
and strive to do my best.
وأسعى جاهداً لبذل قصارى جهدي.
Well then,
حسناً إذاً،
now tell me about
والآن أخبرني عن
your career plan for the next five years.
خطتك المهنية للسنوات الخمس القادمة.
To, together with the company,
بالتعاون مع الشركة،
learn,
يتعلم،
love,
حب،
and the ability to be loved.
والقدرة على أن يكون المرء محبوباً.
To jointly incubate some
للاحتضان المشترك لبعض
resounding...
مدوٍ...
projects.
مشاريع.
It's "resounding".
إنه "مدوٍ".
"Resounding"...
"مدوي"...
Like a newborn baby's cry...
مثل بكاء طفل حديث الولادة...
"Resounding".
"مدوٍ".
Also, I think your planning timeframe is a bit short.
أعتقد أيضاً أن الإطار الزمني للتخطيط قصير بعض الشيء.
If possible,
إذا كان ذلك ممكنا،
I hope it's forever.
أتمنى أن يدوم ذلك للأبد.
Last question.
السؤال الأخير.
Do you have
هل لديك
any other job offers in hand?
هل لديك أي عروض عمل أخرى؟
Just this one.
هذا واحد فقط.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I've finished my questions.
لقد انتهيت من أسئلتي.
Now it's your turn to ask.
والآن حان دورك لتسأل.
Will you marry me?
هل ستتزوجني؟
If
لو
you feel I'm not yet qualified, that's okay.
إذا كنت تشعر أنني لست مؤهلاً بعد، فلا بأس.
You don't have to sign yet.
لستَ مضطراً للتوقيع الآن.
At worst, I'll just keep interning.
في أسوأ الأحوال، سأستمر في التدريب.
But I will always stand
لكنني سأبقى دائماً صامداً
wherever your gaze can reach,
أينما يصل نظرك،
waiting for your answer.
في انتظار ردك.